<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>OpenInfraDays Mexico 2022</title>
    <link href="https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io" />
    <updated>2022-06-17T21:35:53-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>OpenInfra Mexico Community</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Sponsors</title>
        <author>
            <name>OpenInfra Mexico Community</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/sponsors.html"/>
        <id>https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/sponsors.html</id>

        <updated>2022-06-17T21:35:42-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Soon... (We hope) If you or your company wants to become one please reach out to us at mkt@openinfradays.mx Tweet
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="align-center">Soon... (We hope)</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/media/posts/4/sticker_10.png" sizes="(min-width: 37.5em) 1600px, 80vw" srcset="https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/media/posts/4/responsive/sticker_10-xs.png 384w ,https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/media/posts/4/responsive/sticker_10-sm.png 600w ,https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/media/posts/4/responsive/sticker_10-md.png 768w ,https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/media/posts/4/responsive/sticker_10-lg.png 1200w ,https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/media/posts/4/responsive/sticker_10-xl.png 1600w"  alt="" width="309" height="309"></figure>
<p class="align-center">If you or your company wants to become one please reach out to us at <a href="mailto:mkt@openinfradays.mx">mkt@openinfradays.mx</a></p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://twitter.com/share?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" class="twitter-share-button" data-size="large" data-via="OpenInfraCDMX" data-hashtags="weareopeninfra" data-show-count="false">Tweet</a>
<script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>OID-MX&#x27;22</title>
        <author>
            <name>OpenInfra Mexico Community</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/about-oid-mexico.html"/>
        <id>https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/about-oid-mexico.html</id>

        <updated>2022-06-17T21:35:28-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Save the date Open Infrastructure Days Mexico edition will be take place on Monday August 15th. Event will be 100%&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Save the date</h2>
<p>Open Infrastructure Days Mexico edition will be take place on Monday August 15th.</p>
<h2>Open Infrastructure Days Mexico Format</h2>
<p>Event will be 100% online only and interactions will be done by real-time chat between speakers and participants, be ready to make and answer questions, share links or even laboratory environments accesses, please always have the <a href="https://openinfra.dev/legal/code-of-conduct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Code of conduct</a> in mind.</p>
<h1>Presentations</h1>
<p>Presentations videos will be prerecorded and shared by the time scheduled, chat rooms will stay open from the beginning of the event and remain open until eternity. We don't need professional setups, just make sure you can record yourself with the background pointing to a wall or something without movement and get a good audio quality, reach out if you have questions or concerts.</p>
<h1>Chat rooms</h1>
<p>We will share a slack invite for all the participants a day before the event opening to be ready to interact and share opinions and questions.</p>
<h1>Code of conduct</h1>
<p>Please see <a href="https://openinfra.dev/legal/code-of-conduct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Code of conduct</a> section.</p>
<h1>Questions</h1>
<p>Send us an e-mail to <a href="mailto:hello@openinfradays.mx">hello@openinfradays.mx</a></p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://twitter.com/share?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" class="twitter-share-button" data-size="large" data-via="OpenInfraCDMX" data-hashtags="weareopeninfra" data-show-count="false">Tweet</a>
<script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Home</title>
        <author>
            <name>OpenInfra Mexico Community</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/home.html"/>
        <id>https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/home.html</id>

        <updated>2022-06-17T21:35:07-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Open Infrastructure Days Mexico 2022 We're OpenInfra / Somos OpenInfra Speak at OID-MX'22 - Submissions Close July 11 23:59 CDT&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h1 class="align-center"><span style="color: #169179;"><strong>Open Infrastructure Days </strong></span><span style="color: #169179;"><strong>Mexico 2022</strong></span></h1>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center">We're OpenInfra / Somos OpenInfra</p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<hr>
<h2>Call for presentations is now Open 🤓</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Speak at OID-MX'22 - Submissions Close July 11 23:59 CDT</p>
</li>
<li>See <a href="https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/call-for-presentations.html">Call for presentations</a> to understand about Categories/Topics for consideration for sessions and case studies.</li>
<li>See <a href="https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/about-oid-mexico.html">About OID Mexico</a> to know more about the event format.</li>
<li>To submit a proposal, please contact: <a href="mailto:speakers@openinfradays.mx" style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">speakers@openinfradays.mx</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>About OID Mexico</h2>
<div class="text">
<p>Open Infrastructure Days is an event organized by Open Infrastructure User Group around the world. And focused on Open Infrastructure Projects and any related topics.</p>
<p>Open Infrastructure Days Mexico is one of the regional Open Infrastructure Days. the event is organized by Open Infrastructure User Groups from several regions in Mexico. And it's focused on community development across Mexico. To union community efforts, to develop Open Infrastructure community, and to provide back to each local user groups in Mexico.</p>
<table class="align-center" style="border-collapse: collapse; width: 100%; border-color: #000000; border-style: solid;" border="1">
<tbody>
<tr style="border-collapse: collapse; width: 100%; border-color: #000000; border-style: solid;">
<td style="width: 33.1507%;"><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mexico_City" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/00/Angel-de-la-Independencia--Mexico-D.F.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="" width="144" height="200"></figure></a></td>
<td style="width: 33.4247%;"><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mexico_City" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/54/Mexico-3271_-_Z%C3%B3calo_%282214738586%29.jpg/450px-Mexico-3271_-_Z%C3%B3calo_%282214738586%29.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  width="150" height="200"></figure></a></td>
<td style="width: 33.4247%;"><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mexico_City" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/0/01/Monumento_a_la_Revoluci%C3%B3n_2_%28cropped%29.jpg/532px-Monumento_a_la_Revoluci%C3%B3n_2_%28cropped%29.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  width="178" height="200"></figure></a></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h2 class="sec-title align-left"><span class="title">About the community</span></h2>
<p>This event is hosted by user groups from</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.meetup.com/OpenInfrastructureCDMX/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Mexico City Meetup Group</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.meetup.com/OpenInfrastructureGDL/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Guadalajara Meetup Group</a></li>
</ul>
<p>For general information about the Open Infrastructure foundation please <a href="https://openinfra.dev/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">click here</a></p>
</div>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://twitter.com/share?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" class="twitter-share-button" data-size="large" data-via="OpenInfraCDMX" data-hashtags="weareopeninfra" data-show-count="false">Tweet</a>
<script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Call for presentations</title>
        <author>
            <name>OpenInfra Mexico Community</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/call-for-presentations.html"/>
        <id>https://alsotoes.github.io/openinfradays-mexico-2022.github.io/call-for-presentations.html</id>

        <updated>2022-06-17T21:35:53-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Open Infrastructure Days Tracks The Open Infrastructure events includes keynotes, presentations, panels, hands-on workshops, and collaborative working sessions covering over&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h1 class="align-center">Open Infrastructure Days Tracks</h1>
<p>The Open Infrastructure events includes keynotes, presentations, panels, hands-on workshops, and collaborative working sessions covering over 30 open source projects. Expect to hear about the intersection of many open source infrastructure projects, including Ceph, Kubernetes, Magma, ONAP, OPNFV and the projects hosted by the OpenInfra Foundation: Airship, Kata Containers, OpenInfra Labs, OpenStack, StarlingX, and Zuul.</p>
<hr>
<h1 class="align-center"><strong>Call for Presentations</strong></h1>
<p><strong>5G, NFV &amp; Edge</strong><br>Topics include: 5G, cloudlet, distributed computing, economics, Mesh, security, networking, architecture, ease of deployment, edge ecosystem, hardware performance accelerators (e.g. GPUs, ASICs, etc.), hardware profile, IoT, low end-to-end latency, management tools, scaling, edge-enabled applications, physical hardening, QoS, remote/extreme environments, remote troubleshooting, standalone cloudlets, tamper evidence, tamper resistance, VM and container handoff across WAN connections, zero-touch provisioning, QoS, SDN, SLAs, standardization e.g. ETSI NFV.</p>
<p><strong>AI, Machine Learning, HPC</strong><br>Topics include: AI, computation, cluster, economics, exascale, government, GPUs, grid, HPC, HTC, machine learning, New applications for AI running on OpenStack clouds, Novel/Emerging architectures for GPUs/AI, operations at scale, performance, scientific research.</p>
<p><strong>CI/CD</strong><br>Topics include: Software development pipeline, automated testing, QA, culture &amp; process, policies &amp; compliance, CI/CD ecosystem, repository architecture, unit vs integration testing, deployment maturity model, gitops.</p>
<p><strong>Container Infrastructure</strong><br>Topics include: Running containers at scale, container ecosystem, container networking, container storage, container security, hybrid VM &amp; container architectures, containers &amp; bare metal.</p>
<p><strong>Getting Started</strong><br>Beginner-level track to learn the basics about all open infrastructure-related topics.</p>
<p><strong>Hands-on Workshops</strong><br>Hands-on Workshops offer a window into training for operators and application developers across different projects. Sessions are typically 90 minutes and require an RSVP and some prep work. Bring your laptop and walk away with the skills you need to become an open source contributor.</p>
<p><strong>Hardware Enablement</strong><br>Topics include: Software components needed to enable hardware in cloud or edge environments, GPUS, DPUs, FPGAs, sustainability, data center operations, hardware standards (Open19, OCP), data center efficiency, server design, SmartNICs, testing and certification.</p>
<p><strong>Open Development</strong><br>Topics include: the 4 opens, the future of free and open source software, challenges of open collaboration, open development best practices and tools, open source governance models, diversity and inclusion, mentoring and outreach, community management.</p>
<p><strong>Private &amp; Hybrid Cloud</strong><br>Topics include: architecture, bare metal, economics, hardware, operations, orchestration &amp; hybrid cloud tools, networking, organizational culture &amp; processes, security &amp; compliance, SLAs, storage, upgrades, user experience, vendor selection.</p>
<p><strong>Public Cloud</strong><br>Topics include: architecture / hardware, economics, cloud portability, features &amp; needs, federation, hardware, operations / upgrades, multi-tenants, networking, performance, scale, security &amp; compliance, SLAs, storage, open source platforms, tools &amp; SDKs, UI / UX, upgrades, user experience.</p>
<p><strong>Security</strong><br>Topics include: Attestation, authenticity, authorization, data protection, encryption, identification, policy enforcement, privacy, regulatory compliance, risk management, trusted computing, vulnerability tracking/mitigation.</p>
<hr>
<h3>FAQ - How to Submit a Proposal that will be Accepted</h3>
<p><strong>Q: Who is the audience for my talk? </strong>A: The Open Infrastructure Days is for people who run and make decisions about IT infrastructure strategy, technologies and vendors. Open source infrastructure is flexible, innovative and interoperable. And it’s made up of many different technologies and providers around the world. </p>
<p><strong>Q: What should my title include? </strong>A: Your title will be used by the attendees to decide among multiple tracks which talk to attend for the next session. It should attract people to your talk. Consider not just the technology as part of the title, but also what you are uniquely bringing to the discussion. A little controversy adds to the attraction. Ending with a question that attendees will want to find the answer to can help.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What should my abstract include? </strong>A: The best abstracts summarize the topic you will present, but also demonstrate that you have the expertise to be "the one" to give a talk on this subject matter. State any prerequisite knowledge that might be required, or if it is an entry-level talk (we need those also), say so. Most abstracts are rejected because we cannot determine whether it will be a good talk or not.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What about my job title? </strong>A: If you have a title with the word "product", "manager", "sales", or "marketing" in it, you may need to go to extra effort in your abstract to convince us that you will give a good technical talk.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What should I include in learning objectives? </strong>A: Each objective should be a concrete insight you expect the audience to gain. This is an additional way to demonstrate your grasp of the subject matter. Do not leave these blank.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Can I have more time to submit? </strong>A: We start evaluating proposals as soon as they are submitted. The earlier you submit, the less competition we have in front of us for the topic you want to present. Later submissions are compared to your early submission. Taking time to do a good job on the proposal will be reflected in your probability of being accepted. Hacking something together at the last minute just prior to the deadline is not a strategy for success.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Contact Information</strong><br>For additional questions, please contact <a href="mailto:speakers@openinfradays.mx">speakers@openinfradays.mx</a></p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://twitter.com/share?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" class="twitter-share-button" data-size="large" data-via="OpenInfraCDMX" data-hashtags="weareopeninfra" data-show-count="false">Tweet</a>
<script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
